TASHAY MYRICK

Chicago, IL, 60637 | 217-848-1335 | myrick_tashay@yahoo.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/tashay-myrick

HUMAN RESOURCE SPECIALIST / HR ASSISTANT

PROFILE

Dedicated and self-motivated individual offering a solid educational background in Human Resources, Healthcare, and Hospitality combined with operations and workflow management experience. Trained to deliver the programs and processes necessary for success. Consistently produce results above client and employer expectation.

HUMAN RESOURCE COMPETENCIES

- Ability to apply applications used in functional areas of Human Resources including payroll
- Understand legally required employee benefits: social security, worker comp and unemployment comp
- Knowledge of voluntary programs: health, disability, life, retirement, time-off, educational, work/life
- Extensive knowledge in recruiting, confidential documentation, screening applications, scheduling
- Thorough understanding of employment and labor laws

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Windows 98/XP, Vista, and 7, Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, Access, Outlook, PowerPoint), type 45 wpm

EDUCATION

MSH, Health Care Administration

Keller Graduate School of Management, Chicago, IL

May 2018

June 2015

MBA, Human Resource Management

Keller Graduate School of Management, Chicago, IL

Bachelor of Science, Hospitality Management

Eastern Illinois University, Charleston, IL

May 2010

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Representative
UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS AT CHICAGO, IL

June 2013 - Present

- Utilizes communication skills to greet and register Pre-operative patients while demonstrating a high level of customer awareness and a strong commitment to fulfilling customer needs. appropriately.
- Collects, analyzes and records patient demographic, insurance, and clinic data in order to register patients for services and establish a billing account.
- Transcribe medical information as needed.
- Utilizes current knowledge of regulatory standards when answering patient inquires.
- Exhibits attention to detail under stressful situations by accurately obtaining and recording data from distressed individuals, thereby increasing speed toward remedying the individual's illness or injury.
- Answers multi-phone lines throughout the hospital pertaining to registration inquires.
- Ensures adherence to patient privacy and HIPAA laws are followed
- Assists in supporting unit patient flow activities such as patient discharge arrangements including prescreens, transport services, record retrieval, etc. as directed by the Clinical Manager/Coordinator

Utilizes appropriate systems: SurgiNet, Cerner, and PAM to maximize delivery of patient care.

Executive Room Attendant, Housekeeping Coordinator, Housekeeping Supervisor Training Sept 2010 – June 2014 THE PALMER HOUSE HILTON HOTEL, CHICAGO, IL

- Operated switchboard, intercom and two-way radio to relay incoming, outgoing and interoffice calls
- Acted as coordinator between departments to ensure rooms are prepared for arrivals
- Record, delegate, and monitor housekeeping productivity for timely completion; Report status of assignments and communicate readiness of units to Front Desk and management;
- Ensure compliance with: Internal Audit, Quality Assurance, Loss Prevention, and Housekeeping Department Operating Procedures.
- Provided information to guests about hotel services, facilities and other amenities

Assistant General Manager

Jan 2004 - June 2010

WHITE CASTLE CORPORATION, CHICAGO, IL

- Administers and executes various day-to-day customer service and support activities for the restaurant
- Managed daily operation of 20 to 30 employees including interviewing, hiring, orientating, leading ,mentoring, and evaluating staff to meet organizational needs.
- Prepares reports and statements to determine daily financial goals
- Controlled P&L by auditing waste and operational sales
- Executes employment, payroll transactions, and scheduling, utilizing HR Enterprise Applications:
 Workflow and HireTouch

Customer Service Representative

May 2009 - Sept 2014

AUBURN GRESHMAN DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION, CHICAGO, IL UNITED STATES

- Provided administrative assistance for staff and organized clerical and administrative work flow process
- Build relationships with clients and vendors through face-to-face interaction
- Provided accounting support including processing vendor payments and completing bank deposits
- Established and maintained office files and planned, organized, and coordinated meetings
- Handled inbound and outbound calls and transferred calls to appropriate personnel
- Scheduled appointments and maintains calendars

PROFESSIONAL ORGANIZATIONS

Society for Human Resource Management(SHRM) 2017-Present Zeta Phi Beta Sorority Incorporated-Public Relations Chair 2008-Present